# **Alex Landa**

## IT Engineer at Qualcomm

# Summary

Customer focused with dedication to regulations and guide lines. Fast learner.

Have recent experience in software troubleshooting, maintenance, and installation on Windows XP and 7 Professional, VM Ware ESX and Fusion, Mac OSX and Linux Red Hat and Ubuntu platforms.

Experience in hardware and software installation, maintenance, and troubleshooting, on Windows, Linux and UNIX based platforms

LAN and wireless infrastructure support as well as interaction with WAN

Experience in multimedia educational software quality assurance.

# Experience

## Senior IT Engineer at QUALCOMM Inc

March 2016 - Present

#### **IT Engineer**

June 2014 - March 2016 (1 year 10 months)

## Senior IT System Specialist at Motorola Mobility / Google

July 2011 - June 2014 (3 years)

Construction of new data center and migration from old data center to new data center in a new building still under construction.

New data center cooling and power/generator tests and verification.

Environmental and structural support of both data centers.

Decommissioning of an old data center.

New Linux standard image creation participation and testing.

Cisco UCS blade server configuration and implementation for the engineering community.

#### **Technical support analyst**

January 2010 - July 2011 (1 year 7 months)

#### Technical support analyst at CSC at Motorola

2006 - 2010 (5 years)

## **Engineering Support Technician at VMware**

August 2005 - January 2006 (6 months)

Provided technical support for users working in VM Ware ESX 2.5, VM Ware GSX 3.2, Linux Red Hat, Suse Linux 9, and Windows XP environments.

Building, configuring and setting up VM Ware ESX and Linux Red Hat servers and Workstations.

Created and reconfigured DNS entries and handled VLAN changes.

Configured SCSI and SATA RAID systems upon request.

Handled computer moves, ads, and modifications on weekly basis.

Regularly interfaced with users, and technicians.

Installed and supported a large variety of software including Microsoft Office XP, Visio, Microsoft Outlook, Internet Explorer, and Putty.

Daily ticket processing.

# Education

# **Institute of Management and Business**

Master, Computer Science and Management, 1997 - 2000

## **First Technical College**

AA, Machine Tool CNC Operation and Troubleshooting, 1994 - 1996

# **Alex Landa**

IT Engineer at Qualcomm



Contact Alex on LinkedIn